thegoodguys.com.au 2017-04-20

# Website Privacy Policy for The Good Guys

The Good Guys have adopted and complies with the Australian Privacy Principles as set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (as amended by the Privacy Amendment (Enhancing Privacy Protection) Act 2012.

### What personal Information does The Good Guys collect and hold about you?

When you visit The Good Guys website the following information will be recorded by our Internet Service Provider (ISP) for statistical purposes:

  * your server address
  * your top level domain name (eg, .com, .gov, .au, etc)
  * the date and time of your visit to the site
  * the pages accessed and documents downloaded
  * the previous site visited, and
  * the type of browser used.

No attempt will be made to identify you or your browsing activities from these records except in the unlikely event of an investigation by the ISP, or where a law enforcement agency exercises a warrant to inspect the Internet Service Provider's logs.

When you make a purchase on The Good Guys website, or send us a message requesting assistance or information about any of our products and/or services, you acknowledge that by providing us with your personal information you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of this information both for the purposes for which it was collected and also to communicate with you about a related or ancillary reason which could include but is not limited to the following reasons:

  * To process and fulfil the order you have placed, including communicating its status, and contacting you about delivery
  * To respond to your request for product or service information
  * The date and time of your visit to the site
  * Administer and manage the services we provide you
  * To third party service providers that assist us with the fulfilment or improvement of our products and services
  * For reporting purposes, or compliance in line with our legal obligations
  * To prevent fraud against yourself, The Good Guys, or another third party
  * To seek your feedback in relation to the products or services you have purchased by way of a product review
  * To improve our website
  * Unless you opt out, to communicate with you on a regular basis about any offers, promotions, products, or services that may be of interest

In order to fulfil all or any of the criteria above, you agree that we may contact you by the most appropriate method and this may include; email, SMS, MMS, mail, social media, or telephone.

### How do The Good Guys collect personal information?

The Good Guys collects personal information directly from you when you submit it either in store, online, or by telephone. We may also collect information from third parties or public sources, such as names, telephone numbers, email addresses and/or social media profile details sourced from organisations with the permission to release this information.

### Information security

We will take all reasonable steps to protect all personal or company information from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

Your information is stored securely whether in an electronic or physical form. For example, only personnel requiring access to the information are allowed access. All personal, company or confidential information is stored in secured premises or in electronic databases requiring logins and passwords.

Some information is kept for a number of years to comply with legal requirements. Any personal information that is no longer needed is destroyed.

### Access and correction

You can request access at any time to view and correct any personal information that we hold. We will process your request promptly within a reasonable time. There is no fee for requesting access to your information. You may ask us at any time to correct personal information held by us about you which is incorrect or out of date.

We aim to ensure that all information we hold, which we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. You should promptly notify us if there are any changes to your personal information.

### Links to other websites

The Good Guys website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by The Good Guys. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites.

### Ratings and Reviews

You acknowledge and agree that The Good Guys reserve the right to publish part or all of any submitted reviews or ratings these may include first name and suburb of participants.

### Changes to The Good Guys Privacy Policy

The Good Guys reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time to meet legislative requirements. If changes are made, they will be reflected here in this policy. You are invited to contact the Privacy Officer at Support Centre by telephone on (03) 9330 5300 or by mail to P.O. Box 154 Niddrie Vic 3042 with any queries.
